<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Jason Daniels, a top Real Estate Agent in Colorado Springs, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 11:09:54 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 11:09:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Properly Prepare for a Buyer’s Appointment</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/11h2G6WcweM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m going to show you how to properly prepare for a buyer’s appointment. I encourage you to have the buyer meet you in your office to show their level of commitment to working with you. If your office is a bit of a long commute, you can meet at a coffee shop or other neutral location that’s closer to them. Keep in mind that safety is of the utmost importance here. Make sure you have materials that show the agent why they should work with you and do a little research about the buyer themself. To learn more, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 09:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-properly-prepare-for-a-buyers-appointment.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-properly-prepare-for-a-buyers-appointment.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Advice for Reaching Out to Home Value Report Leads</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JoQcIt4epkE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to quickly reach out to talk to you about the follow-up process for a home value report. Most of these websites will send out an automated report, but sometimes it will just be an email to you with the information. You definitely want to follow up immediately and treat them like a normal internet lead. Thank them for registering for your website, let them know about their automated value report, and that you can come out to do an analysis for a more detailed evaluation. To learn more about the process and some best practices, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 09:00:41 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/advice-for-reaching-out-to-home-value-report-leads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/advice-for-reaching-out-to-home-value-report-leads.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Knowing What Type of Content to Share</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kzdA4Piwm-w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;Not all content is good content. Today I&amp;rsquo;m sharing how to know the difference and better engage with your sphere.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a real estate agent, we must engage with our sphere regularly. The challenge with that, of course, is crafting meaningful content that provides your clients with value. Here are some tips for content creation: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educate your audience about the housing market, real estate, and upcoming listings.&lt;/strong&gt; Highlight interesting trends in the housing market and offer expert analysis and predictions. We don’t want to just repeatedly send them listings—they can look for those elsewhere. While it’s important to occasionally send them listings so that they know you’re actively involved in the business, adding the extra touch of, say, a video blog or an interesting social media post can be impactful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Don’t overrun your personal social media page with business.%20http://localhost:4000/knowing-what-type-of-content-to-share.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Don’t overrun your personal social media page with business.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, whatever you send through—whether via postcards in the U.S. mail or newsletters via email—should be carefully thought out. There’s an infamous story about an agent who sent out recipe cards for 10 years, only to find out that someone in their sphere all along chose a different Realtor for their home sale. When confronted, the person told this agent, “Oops, I forgot you were a Realtor. I thought you were involved with some cooking school.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That story illustrates &lt;strong&gt;the importance of keeping your content industry-related.&lt;/strong&gt; On your personal social media accounts, follow this general rule: Make one business post for every three to four personal posts. Don’t overrun your personal page with business, as it will likely annoy your friends and potential clients. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buyers and sellers, millennials especially, want to see that you’re a real person and not some scam; you need to be active on the most popular social media platforms. On them, you can highlight local businesses or plug upcoming client events. Truly, there’s no limit to the amount of valuable information you can share with your sphere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please reach out via phone, email, or the links below. I’d be happy to talk with you about how to best contact your sphere and strengthen your business relationships. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 16:52:53 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/knowing-what-type-of-content-to-share.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/knowing-what-type-of-content-to-share.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quick Tips to Boost Your Referral Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kxdE0EByFuE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;How do you ask for referrals? Today I&amp;rsquo;ll share my tips and best practices.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re reluctant to ask for more referrals, there are a few simple things you can try to increase your referral business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, have a conversation with your friends and family. Ask if they know anyone interested in buying or selling property.  If they do, do they have a Realtor to help them? This way, you’re letting them know that you’re looking for referrals, which might be easier to get from a trusted source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also ask past clients for referrals. &lt;strong&gt;It’s important to let them know at the very beginning of the transaction that you work by referral&lt;/strong&gt; and remind them through the process. To increase the frequency with which you can get referrals from past clients, make sure their experience is superior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Be sure to reach out consistently throughout the process.%20http://localhost:4000/quick-tips-to-boost-your-referral-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Be sure to reach out consistently throughout the process.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research shows when someone is looking for a specific thing, like a car, they’ll start to see it everywhere. Similarly, when someone is shopping for a home, their ears are always open for conversations about real estate, be it at work, church, or wherever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transactions can take anywhere from 30 to 90 days, so be sure to reach out consistently throughout the process. I can’t tell you how much that has helped my business grow. Other things, like &lt;strong&gt;handwritten notes and even housecalls, can help you get referrals,&lt;/strong&gt; as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about getting more referrals, we offer training courses here at RE/MAX Millennium. Feel free to reach out to us to schedule a consultation or to address any other questions you have.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 11:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/quick-tips-to-boost-your-referral-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quick-tips-to-boost-your-referral-business.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Do You Increase Your Odds of Getting a Review?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FaDfldyAfQI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;Here are a few quick tips that will help you get more reviews.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know that with the advent of social media and the rise of sites like Yelp and Zillow, reviews have become increasingly important to real estate agents. What’s the key to getting more, better reviews, though?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;you need to provide the best customer service possible.&lt;/strong&gt; This is an obvious tip, but you need to be professional and follow up with people. The very first time you meet with them, tell them you appreciate their time and that you’ll be asking for a review toward the end of the process. I know you like to get reviews on different platforms, but I recommend picking just two or three of them. In addition to Zillow and Yelp, Google and Facebook are good options. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve found that if you ask them for a review right before closing (not at closing—that should be about them), they’re more willing to give you one. If you ask for one after the closing, it might be a while before you get one because at that point they’re more concerned with unpacking and settling into their new home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You need to be professional and follow up with people.%20http://localhost:4000/how-do-you-increase-your-odds-of-getting-a-review.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You need to be professional and follow up with people.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another good way to get reviews is to &lt;strong&gt;hold a contest centered around them.&lt;/strong&gt; You can’t just ask for a five-star review—federal law prohibits that—but you can offer prizes like an overnight hotel stay or an iPad for any past clients who write you a review. All you have to do is send out a video just like this one where you thank them for their business and ask them for honest reviews on the platforms you’ve already picked. You’d be surprised at how many you can get. Before you do this, though, check with your broker to make sure you’re not breaking any federal or state laws. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next time you host a client party, you can also ask past clients to write a review before they attend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just a few ideas to keep in mind, but if you’d like to talk more about this subject, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to schedule a consultation with you and do everything I can to help generate the best reviews possible. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 08:54:44 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-do-you-increase-your-odds-of-getting-a-review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-do-you-increase-your-odds-of-getting-a-review.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using a Dialer</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0YToEDXZzlE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Whether or not you should use a dialer depends on the marketing you do.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should you use a dialer? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case you don’t know, a dialer is a system that automatically dials lists for you. It helps you be more efficient, and most of them have a built-in CRM, as well, so you can track notes. If you want to get really fancy, you can buy a triple-line dialer that can call three people at a time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, &lt;strong&gt;whether you should use a dialer or not depends on the type of marketing you do.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re just reaching out to your sphere and checking in with them, you don’t really need one. It might help if you have 300 or 400 clients and you need to call all of them for a single event, though. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Dialers are typically meant for circle prospecting and cold calling.%20http://localhost:4000/using-a-dialer.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Dialers are typically meant for circle prospecting and cold calling.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, dialers are typically meant for circle prospecting and cold calling—any scenario that involves reaching out to a large volume of people. The system I like to use is called Mojo Dialer, but I’ve also used the RedX Storm® Dialer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to know more about specific dialers my team and I use, and how we use them, give me a call. They’re a handy tool to have to make your business more efficient. If you don’t need to make a lot of large dials, though, you’ll be fine focusing on your sphere by just picking up your phone the old-fashioned way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have questions about any other topic, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to help you. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/using-a-dialer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/using-a-dialer.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Value of Scripts</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/I4nYNBFZswI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s important to learn scripts as an agent, but you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t sound robotic when using them.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an agent, you absolutely should use scripts when dealing with clients, but you shouldn’t sound canned when using them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s important to learn scripts&lt;/strong&gt; because real estate boils down to a couple of different buying and selling processes, and the average consumer will have the same questions and objections depending on whether they’re buying or selling. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once in a while, you’ll get a question or objection you’ve never dealt with, but most agents develop scripts and dialogues to address the majority of their clients’ concerns. It’s our professional duty to focus on understanding our clients’ needs, and by learning scripts, we can listen to their needs when they’re talking to us instead of trying to think of what to say next. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re able to answer your clients’ objections professionally they’ll know that you know what you’re talking about.%20http://localhost:4000/the-value-of-scripts.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re able to answer your clients’ objections professionally they’ll know that you know what you’re talking about.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’d like to see some of the scripts my team and I use, &lt;a href=&quot;https://realestatecareersincolorado.com/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;use this link&lt;/a&gt; to schedule a consultation.&lt;/strong&gt; We practice our scripts daily, and we have different scripts for all types of clients and objections. Like I said, you don’t want to sound canned, which is why I advise that you keep the key elements of the script the same, but alter your responses so they feel like they’re coming from &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re able to answer your clients’ objections professionally they’ll know that you know what you’re talking about. By sounding more professional, you’ll have more success converting your clients. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have more questions about the value of scripts or you have any other real estate needs at all, feel free to call or email me. I’d love to speak with you. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-value-of-scripts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-value-of-scripts.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Contact Expired Leads</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hVRhnM106Rk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s message is about how to prospect expired leads.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to discuss how to go about prospecting expired leads. &lt;strong&gt;If you don’t have a large sphere of clients,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;going after expired listings&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;is o&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ne of the lowest-hanging fruits you can grab at.&lt;/strong&gt; The basic method of getting expired listings is consistent followups. The number one way real estate agents get in touch with expired listings is by simply calling them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Whatever you do, you need to be consistent.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-contact-expired-leads.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Whatever you do, you need to be consistent.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are multiple services out there like REDX or Vulcan7 that you can subscribe to for a fairly affordable rate, and they’ll deliver to you, through their site or your email, expired listings from that day. You can also go back and see past expired listings to call. There are different methods you can employ, but that first day you should reach out three to five times by phone. The second approach is mailing postcards or letters. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are different systems, coaches, and so on you can buy, but find one that works for you. Whatever you do, you need to be consistent. Don’t just call them the day the listing expires, you want to follow up every day or every other day with a text, call, or email. &lt;strong&gt;You can find out more information about them by just looking on Facebook.&lt;/strong&gt; We call that research, it’s not stalking. Do your homework. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most aggressive way that I’ve heard of is literally going and knocking on the door. Devise an explanation of how you’re great at selling homes that didn’t sell the first time and create a pre-listing package. Frequently my team and I are the second or third Realtors people come to, and we share our success stories with them of how we were able to sell former clients’ homes for full price in 30 days when it was expired once or twice before. &lt;strong&gt;Share how you’re different from their last Realtor&lt;/strong&gt; and can be trusted. Show them your value. They don’t necessarily need to know how many homes you’ve sold, they want to know you care and that you’re going to be there for them and not leave them hanging like their previous Realtor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to pick up the phone and call or stop by the office and I can show you what we do to find expired leads. Also, reach out by phone or email with questions or go to our website and schedule a consultation. I’d love to meet with you. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-contact-expired-leads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-contact-expired-leads.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Content Should You Send Your Farm?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FguxKxGY0Lo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;The content you send your farm shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be exactly the same as the content you send your sphere. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about why.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you send out content to your farm, the information you send them should be a little different from the things you send your sphere, in general. This is because &lt;strong&gt;farms are restricted to a geographic area, whereas your sphere is just a collection of people you’ve connected with. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, the content you send your farm should be a reflection of where they live. This might mean sending out a newsletter detailing area sales activity, video market updates, or notices about local events. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The content you send your farm should be a reflection of where they live.%20http://localhost:4000/what-content-should-you-send-your-farm.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The content you send your farm should be a reflection of where they live.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People tend to be most interested in content that relates to their neighborhood&lt;/strong&gt;, which can work to your advantage as an agent if you happen to have any listings in the area. If you’re able to secure email addresses from people within your farm, giving them email invites to open houses is another great idea. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:53:12 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-content-should-you-send-your-farm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-content-should-you-send-your-farm.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Many Touches Should You Have With Your Farm?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VRWxsDnAkwE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;How many touches should you have with your farm? Here are my thoughts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a question for you agents out there: When it comes to your farm, how many touches should you have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With your sphere of influence, we always encourage you to have 30 or more contacts a year between calls, emails, newsletters, postcards, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Send out something in the physical mail once a month, or once a quarter at a minimum.%20http://localhost:4000/how-many-touches-should-you-have-with-your-farm.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Send out something in the physical mail once a month, or once a quarter at a minimum.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your geographical farm, however, &lt;strong&gt;it’s great to have at least 18 to 24 touches.&lt;/strong&gt; Depending on the size of the farm, it might be more feasible to do more or less. If you’re just starting a farm that includes between 50 and 300 people, you’ll probably want to have more contacts. If you’re farming a wider area, you may not be able to have as many contacts with your base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I recommend: Send out something in the physical mail once a month, or once a quarter at a minimum, and &lt;strong&gt;if you have the phone numbers from your farm, try getting in touch with each person four times a year&lt;/strong&gt;. You could also try walking through the neighborhood to do some door-knocking; this will also help you get to know the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about the specific content that we send out to our farms or anything else related to keeping in touch with your farm, don’t hesitate to reach out to us for a consultation. We’d be happy to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-many-touches-should-you-have-with-your-farm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-many-touches-should-you-have-with-your-farm.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
