<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Jason Daniels, a top Real Estate Agent in Colorado Springs, shares his/her own internal real estate agent training for free. His/Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 16:42:41 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 16:42:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Become a Top Producer Like Me?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CZWPnU0n7Xc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got my start in real estate back in 2003, when I had just moved back to Colorado Springs and didn’t have a lot of prospects. Through grit, determination, and the help of my mentor and father, Brian Daniels, I learned the ropes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My father told me that he wouldn’t give me a business, but would instead make me earn it. The interesting thing was that everyone he knew was already on his list of clients, meaning that I’d have to create a whole new sphere of influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started out selling homes, I was working mostly through referrals, making calls, writing notes, pop-bys, and expanding my sphere. I would ask the people I contacted “If you had a family member or friend who was going to buy a home, do you have a Realtor you would refer to them?” That way, I could avoid asking them directly if they were planning to sell their home—doing that on a regular basis might have inclined them to start avoiding my calls and emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there. I would decide how many homes I wanted to sell, come up with a gameplan, and set myself to work every morning and afternoon answering calls and emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be a top producer, it takes a couple things beyond just grit, determination, and professionalism. I recommend those who want to become high-level agents in the industry to get their education. I don’t just mean the continuing education that the state requires, but also diving in deep to learn more about the industry. Classes are available at title companies and seminars for you to delve into certain topics to enhance your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there.%20http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-become-top-producer-like-me.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, once it’s within your budget, you might consider traveling to other areas of the country for conferences, networking, and coaching from other top producers around the nation. I’ve had many different coaches throughout the years, and I definitely recommend serious agents find their own mentors to learn from their knowledge and expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing this myself, I’ve managed to build up an agent network from which I get referrals. It’s also how I started to build my own team, which allowed us to do more expansive marketing campaigns to garner more leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be a top producer in Colorado Springs, you also need to learn how to play nicely with others. Yes, we do represent our clients’ best interests, but there’s a certain way that high-level agents need to handle themselves during transactions. When we work peer-to-peer and Realtor-to-Realtor, we want to maintain a professional relationship. The MLS is, after all, a cooperative resource that is best utilized when we all work well together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, if you make goals, find a mentor or coach, work hard, start with people you know to build your database, and continue in that fashion, you can become a top producer in the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need any advice about how to advance your own career as an agent, please feel free to reach out to me. Indeed, that’s why I started this brokerage: I wanted to help more agents reach their goals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-become-top-producer-like-me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-become-top-producer-like-me.html</guid>
        
        <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Client Events Are a Great Tool for Agents</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xrMaHQ9nBeU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hear this question a lot from my fellow agents: Should I hold client events?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Absolutely! If you want to grow your referral base, these events are crucial. We do four major events each year, but you don’t need a huge budget to host something great. Starting out with a simple happy hour gathering for your best clients can be a great way to test the waters. Then, you can focus on bigger, better events for your entire client list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the things we like to do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A chocolate giveaway in February alongside a party in our office
A family-friendly night at the movies in June where we rent out multiple theaters
A barbecue extravaganza in August where we go all out with big giveaways, plenty of food, and fun for all
A pie giveaway around Thanksgiving&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You don’t need a huge budget to host something great.%20http://localhost:4000/events-are-perfect-for-bringing.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You don’t need a huge budget to host something great.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s always good to have small get-togethers to supplement these big events. Take your biggest clients and go golfing, attend a sporting event, etc. Don’t overspend, and absolutely do not forget to follow up after these events. Thank them for coming, share pictures of the event, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need further information about making your business more successful, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to helping you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/events-are-perfect-for-bringing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events-are-perfect-for-bringing.html</guid>
        
        <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Best Sources for Listing Leads</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/61vw4qJ2GvQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m excited to talk about some of the top sources for listing leads. Here’s my list for all of the other agents out there:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Sphere and past clients.&lt;/strong&gt; I can’t stress this enough. Embrace and engage with your sphere and past clients. When you talk to them, make sure they know you’re never too busy for their referrals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. A network of agents.&lt;/strong&gt; 10 years ago, this was a lot harder to do because you had to do it in person. With the advent of social media, it’s much easier. I do recommend meeting people in person when you can, but it really makes sense to reach out to agents in communities where military homebuyers are coming into Colorado Springs. Do your research and start finding these Realtors on Facebook and LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3+4. FSBO/Expired.&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of people don’t like working these lists, but they should. These are two groups of people who you already know want to sell their home. In the last year, we’ve seen more people using a Realtor than in the previous 10+ years. Things are getting a little bit more complicated in terms of marketing, so these types of home sellers want expert advice. Nine times out of 10, I find that expired listings happen because of the previous agent’s error. The key is to pick one strategy and stick to it. Don’t get distracted by shiny objects. Just find a system and stick to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Building a network of agents is much easier these days.%20http://localhost:4000/4-best-sources-for-listing-leads.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Building a network of agents is much easier these days.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about any of these strategies or anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email today. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 12:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/4-best-sources-for-listing-leads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/4-best-sources-for-listing-leads.html</guid>
        
        <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Many Benefits My Brokerage Provides to Agents</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IFViKM9WbIo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What value can our brokerage provide you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have the best value given our fees here at RE/MAX. In fact, the average agent here in Colorado Springs sells about 6 homes per year, but our agents sell over 26 homes per year on average.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a reason for that: One of the No. 1 things we focus on here is training, which is covered for you. We do weekly and monthly trainings, though none of it is mandatory if you don’t want to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also strive to keep things fresh and new. Other brokerages in town rehash the same materials over and over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RE/MAX Millennium makes an active effort to be on the cutting-edge technology, which is critical for your success, especially with the way the market is shifting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.%20http://localhost:4000/as-broker-owner-of-remax-millennium-i.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of that, we have administrative staff who help you from the front end by greeting your clients, as well as the back end, where they take care of all your paperwork and ensure that you’re compliant with laws and procedures. We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we have, hands down, the nicest office. This is not me boasting—I have been told this by many people. We even have an open cafe space where our agents can hang out together with clients. We also host our client appreciation events and parties right here in the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our brokerage prides itself on building a community in which our agents know that they’ll help each other out. In fact, among our core values as a company are transparency and willingness to help others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just a few snippets of the values and benefits you stand to gain by working with us here at RE/MAX Millennium. If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us here. I’d be happy to have a conversation with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 13:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/as-broker-owner-of-remax-millennium-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/as-broker-owner-of-remax-millennium-i.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another Successful Event for Colorado Springs Business Owners</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Wauk4AmJGDw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit, and it was a resounding success. I started promoting it because I wanted to bring together small businesses and put on a great event with a national speaker without having to drive to Denver. Through technology, marketing, and networking, we all learned a lot about what it takes to grow your business in today’s economic climate. We’re so happy that so many of you were able to join us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 11:02:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/another-successful-event-for-colorado.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/another-successful-event-for-colorado.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buyers Agents vs. Listing Agents: What Should a New Real Estate Professional Become?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-u9JMpcFTeg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People just entering the real estate industry may wonder what role within the profession would be best for them. Actually, the best way to answer this question is by asking yourself a couple of others. For example: Do you want to be on a team? If so, becoming a buyer’s agent or a listing agent may be a good option. Being a listing agent will allow you to leverage your time, money, and efforts more quickly, but most agents start out working with buyers. If you’d like to learn more or have any other questions, we would be happy to schedule an appointment and talk about this topic in greater depth.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/buyers-agents-vs-listing-agents-what.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/buyers-agents-vs-listing-agents-what.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Most Effective Way to Become a Licensed Realtor</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KPCQUxCUAGc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re wanting to get into the real estate business, there are a few options you have when you’re first starting out. Today, we’ll be discussing the ways you can begin your career as a Realtor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To earn your license, you’ll typically go attend a course for around three weeks and for eight hours a day. You’ll then take a test a become a licensed real estate agent. Here in Colorado Springs, there are several in-person programs you can choose from. My agents have found success in Kaplan, and I personally recommend this option. On top of in-person classes, they also have an online component and correspondence courses. Other real estate schools usually have these components as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests.%20http://localhost:4000/the-most-effective-way-to-become.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I’ve found that agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests. This is primarily because they’re missing out on vital interaction with an instructor and other benefits of the classroom setting. Correspondence courses, where students are essentially just reading a book, show high failure rates. The online component fares a bit better, but neither option compares to the in-person experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaplan’s in-person courses see students passing the first or second time, compared to other options where tests are often retaken multiple times. If you want to be better prepared for the final exam, you want to devote three weeks and show up to an in-person class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to contact us. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-most-effective-way-to-become.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-most-effective-way-to-become.html</guid>
        
        <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Keys to Making Your Morning Routine More Productive</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wHeOpEp93v8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the three components laid out in the book “The Miracle Morning” by Hal Elrod:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Read (spiritual or motivational reading)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;2. Exercise&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;3. Coordinate the rest of your day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the same routine that I follow every morning. After I wake up at 5:30, I go to the gym and get a workout in. Then I head back home and read scripture and/or part of whatever motivational book I’m reading at the time. I’m learning more and more about meditation, so that’s also something you could try for this step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When coordinating your day, sit down and fill out your “Dominate Your Day” sheet that I talked about in a previous video. When you plan your day ahead of time, you can focus on it before it gets away from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.%20http://localhost:4000/3-keys-to-making-your-morning-routine.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have kids, wake up however early you need to to get this done before they get up. The one thing you don’t want to do first thing in the morning is check your smartphone. If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to talk more about how you can make your morning routine more productive or you have any other questions about this topic, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be glad to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 14:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-keys-to-making-your-morning-routine.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/3-keys-to-making-your-morning-routine.html</guid>
        
        <category>Life Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Can Our Office Provide for You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/teeEqU9iMKM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp;amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 09:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-office-provide-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-office-provide-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Key Tips That Will Help You Create a Productive Work Environment</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BmQJrOYXXvM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schedule a free business consultation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling your Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradohomesvalue.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Get a free home value report&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;
Buying a Colorado home? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coloradospringstophomes.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Search all homes for sale&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to grow your business, you need to have a productive work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some agents like to work from home, and that’s okay. Others like to have their office in an office. Here at RE/MAX Millennium, we offer both options. Either way, you’ll find a great work environment, and in our office, we have a cafe space, inviting decor, and a wonderful administrative team to support all our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, here are a couple tips to help you ensure a productive work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=CREATE A PRODUCTIVE WORK ENVIRONMENT.%20http://localhost:4000/key-tips-that-will-help-you-create.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“CREATE A PRODUCTIVE WORK ENVIRONMENT.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you work from home and that’s important to you, you should treat your workday just like you would anywhere else. If you’d wear a suit and tie to the office, wear a suit and tie at home. Dress how you’d normally dress, whether you have an appointment or not. Otherwise, you might find yourself sitting on the couch with a bag of Doritos watching TV when you should be prospecting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also important to have a regimented schedule when you work from home. If you have small children at home or you don’t have your own workspace there, you need to make sure you have a space in the office where you can actually get work done. Stay focused and don’t let yourself get distracted by emails or your smartphone (it’s not so “smart” if it’s distracting you).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studies have shown that there’s no such thing as multitasking, so take 60- to 90-minute periods throughout the day to focus on one thing. I promise you that if you do this, your productivity will increase, and I have plenty of other productivity hacks that I’d be happy to share with you if you’re interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/key-tips-that-will-help-you-create.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/key-tips-that-will-help-you-create.html</guid>
        
        <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
