<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs Real Estate Podcast with Jason Daniels</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jason Daniels</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-03-26 10:11:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jason Daniels</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>JasonDaniels@remax.net</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jason Daniels</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Colorado Springs Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Key to Success Is Staying Focused</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-key-to-success-is-staying-focused.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-24 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We’ve found that with all these new tech toys and social media platforms, there are so many distractions in the world of real estate.

To help hone their focus, I have our agents sit down and write out the top three areas they want to focus on in their business. Once they figure out what they want to do, whether it be FSBOs, expireds, internet leads, or working by referral, we challenge them to divert their focus to those three areas. If they’re a new agent, we ask them to pick three pillars of business that they think they’d like.

We have different advanced courses where we can break up the year, but concentrating on three areas is a good way of keeping things simple.

But what does it mean to focus?

For our part, my team likes to come into the office, get their things ready, do a quick team huddle to see how things are going, and then do a little bit of script and role-play practice.

“Focusing on new business and new client acquisition are both key to maintaining success.”

From 9 a.m. to 11 a.m. Monday to Friday, also called our “power hour,” our focus is on the phones, where we call our internet leads and personal spheres to work referrals. During that time, we also write handwritten notes to thank our clients and those who are referred to us.

After the power hour, we go over scripts and role playing again, just to see how things when.

From there on out, the agents go off to do whatever they need for the rest of the day—listing appointments, buyer appointments, inspections, and so on. 

The great thing about this system is that by the time our agents are free to go out and complete their tasks, they’ll already have done the most important thing of the day, which is focusing on new business and new client acquisition. Both are key to maintaining success.

If you have any questions about focusing on what matters the most in our business, feel free to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Let’s talk about focus.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Let’s talk about focus.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Become a Top Producer Like Me?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-become-top-producer-like-me.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-11 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


I got my start in real estate back in 2003, when I had just moved back to Colorado Springs and didn’t have a lot of prospects. Through grit, determination, and the help of my mentor and father, Brian Daniels, I learned the ropes.

My father told me that he wouldn’t give me a business, but would instead make me earn it. The interesting thing was that everyone he knew was already on his list of clients, meaning that I’d have to create a whole new sphere of influence.

When I started out selling homes, I was working mostly through referrals, making calls, writing notes, pop-bys, and expanding my sphere. I would ask the people I contacted “If you had a family member or friend who was going to buy a home, do you have a Realtor you would refer to them?” That way, I could avoid asking them directly if they were planning to sell their home—doing that on a regular basis might have inclined them to start avoiding my calls and emails.

Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there. I would decide how many homes I wanted to sell, come up with a gameplan, and set myself to work every morning and afternoon answering calls and emails.

To be a top producer, it takes a couple things beyond just grit, determination, and professionalism. I recommend those who want to become high-level agents in the industry to get their education. I don’t just mean the continuing education that the state requires, but also diving in deep to learn more about the industry. Classes are available at title companies and seminars for you to delve into certain topics to enhance your business.

“Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there.”

Additionally, once it’s within your budget, you might consider traveling to other areas of the country for conferences, networking, and coaching from other top producers around the nation. I’ve had many different coaches throughout the years, and I definitely recommend serious agents find their own mentors to learn from their knowledge and expertise.

Doing this myself, I’ve managed to build up an agent network from which I get referrals. It’s also how I started to build my own team, which allowed us to do more expansive marketing campaigns to garner more leads.

To be a top producer in Colorado Springs, you also need to learn how to play nicely with others. Yes, we do represent our clients’ best interests, but there’s a certain way that high-level agents need to handle themselves during transactions. When we work peer-to-peer and Realtor-to-Realtor, we want to maintain a professional relationship. The MLS is, after all, a cooperative resource that is best utilized when we all work well together.

Ultimately, if you make goals, find a mentor or coach, work hard, start with people you know to build your database, and continue in that fashion, you can become a top producer in the field.

If you have any questions or need any advice about how to advance your own career as an agent, please feel free to reach out to me. Indeed, that’s why I started this brokerage: I wanted to help more agents reach their goals.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Client Events Are a Great Tool for Agents</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/events-are-perfect-for-bringing.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-31 15:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


I hear this question a lot from my fellow agents: Should I hold client events?

Absolutely! If you want to grow your referral base, these events are crucial. We do four major events each year, but you don’t need a huge budget to host something great. Starting out with a simple happy hour gathering for your best clients can be a great way to test the waters. Then, you can focus on bigger, better events for your entire client list.

Here are some of the things we like to do:

A chocolate giveaway in February alongside a party in our office
A family-friendly night at the movies in June where we rent out multiple theaters
A barbecue extravaganza in August where we go all out with big giveaways, plenty of food, and fun for all
A pie giveaway around Thanksgiving

“You don’t need a huge budget to host something great.”

It’s always good to have small get-togethers to supplement these big events. Take your biggest clients and go golfing, attend a sporting event, etc. Don’t overspend, and absolutely do not forget to follow up after these events. Thank them for coming, share pictures of the event, and so on.

If you have any questions or need further information about making your business more successful, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to helping you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>4 Best Sources for Listing Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/4-best-sources-for-listing-leads.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-14 12:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I’m excited to talk about some of the top sources for listing leads. Here’s my list for all of the other agents out there:

1. Sphere and past clients. I can’t stress this enough. Embrace and engage with your sphere and past clients. When you talk to them, make sure they know you’re never too busy for their referrals.

2. A network of agents. 10 years ago, this was a lot harder to do because you had to do it in person. With the advent of social media, it’s much easier. I do recommend meeting people in person when you can, but it really makes sense to reach out to agents in communities where military homebuyers are coming into Colorado Springs. Do your research and start finding these Realtors on Facebook and LinkedIn.

3+4. FSBO/Expired. A lot of people don’t like working these lists, but they should. These are two groups of people who you already know want to sell their home. In the last year, we’ve seen more people using a Realtor than in the previous 10+ years. Things are getting a little bit more complicated in terms of marketing, so these types of home sellers want expert advice. Nine times out of 10, I find that expired listings happen because of the previous agent’s error. The key is to pick one strategy and stick to it. Don’t get distracted by shiny objects. Just find a system and stick to it.

“Building a network of agents is much easier these days.”

If you have any questions about any of these strategies or anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email today. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Many Benefits My Brokerage Provides to Agents</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/as-broker-owner-of-remax-millennium-i.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-17 13:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


What value can our brokerage provide you?

We have the best value given our fees here at RE/MAX. In fact, the average agent here in Colorado Springs sells about 6 homes per year, but our agents sell over 26 homes per year on average.

There’s a reason for that: One of the No. 1 things we focus on here is training, which is covered for you. We do weekly and monthly trainings, though none of it is mandatory if you don’t want to participate.

We also strive to keep things fresh and new. Other brokerages in town rehash the same materials over and over.

RE/MAX Millennium makes an active effort to be on the cutting-edge technology, which is critical for your success, especially with the way the market is shifting.

“We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.”

On top of that, we have administrative staff who help you from the front end by greeting your clients, as well as the back end, where they take care of all your paperwork and ensure that you’re compliant with laws and procedures. We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.

Finally, we have, hands down, the nicest office. This is not me boasting—I have been told this by many people. We even have an open cafe space where our agents can hang out together with clients. We also host our client appreciation events and parties right here in the office.

Our brokerage prides itself on building a community in which our agents know that they’ll help each other out. In fact, among our core values as a company are transparency and willingness to help others.

These are just a few snippets of the values and benefits you stand to gain by working with us here at RE/MAX Millennium. If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us here. I’d be happy to have a conversation with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Another Successful Event for Colorado Springs Business Owners</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/another-successful-event-for-colorado.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-27 11:02:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit, and it was a resounding success. I started promoting it because I wanted to bring together small businesses and put on a great event with a national speaker without having to drive to Denver. Through technology, marketing, and networking, we all learned a lot about what it takes to grow your business in today’s economic climate. We’re so happy that so many of you were able to join us.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Buyers Agents vs. Listing Agents: What Should a New Real Estate Professional Become?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/buyers-agents-vs-listing-agents-what.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-21 12:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


People just entering the real estate industry may wonder what role within the profession would be best for them. Actually, the best way to answer this question is by asking yourself a couple of others. For example: Do you want to be on a team? If so, becoming a buyer’s agent or a listing agent may be a good option. Being a listing agent will allow you to leverage your time, money, and efforts more quickly, but most agents start out working with buyers. If you’d like to learn more or have any other questions, we would be happy to schedule an appointment and talk about this topic in greater depth.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Most Effective Way to Become a Licensed Realtor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-most-effective-way-to-become.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-08 11:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you’re wanting to get into the real estate business, there are a few options you have when you’re first starting out. Today, we’ll be discussing the ways you can begin your career as a Realtor.

To earn your license, you’ll typically go attend a course for around three weeks and for eight hours a day. You’ll then take a test a become a licensed real estate agent. Here in Colorado Springs, there are several in-person programs you can choose from. My agents have found success in Kaplan, and I personally recommend this option. On top of in-person classes, they also have an online component and correspondence courses. Other real estate schools usually have these components as well.

“Agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests.”

However, I’ve found that agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests. This is primarily because they’re missing out on vital interaction with an instructor and other benefits of the classroom setting. Correspondence courses, where students are essentially just reading a book, show high failure rates. The online component fares a bit better, but neither option compares to the in-person experience.

Kaplan’s in-person courses see students passing the first or second time, compared to other options where tests are often retaken multiple times. If you want to be better prepared for the final exam, you want to devote three weeks and show up to an in-person class.

If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to contact us. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Keys to Making Your Morning Routine More Productive</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-keys-to-making-your-morning-routine.html</link>
        
          <category>Life Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-22 14:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Follow the three components laid out in the book “The Miracle Morning” by Hal Elrod:

1. Read (spiritual or motivational reading)
2. Exercise
3. Coordinate the rest of your day

This is the same routine that I follow every morning. After I wake up at 5:30, I go to the gym and get a workout in. Then I head back home and read scripture and/or part of whatever motivational book I’m reading at the time. I’m learning more and more about meditation, so that’s also something you could try for this step.

When coordinating your day, sit down and fill out your “Dominate Your Day” sheet that I talked about in a previous video. When you plan your day ahead of time, you can focus on it before it gets away from you.

“If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.”

If you have kids, wake up however early you need to to get this done before they get up. The one thing you don’t want to do first thing in the morning is check your smartphone. If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.

If you’d like to talk more about how you can make your morning routine more productive or you have any other questions about this topic, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be glad to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Can Our Office Provide for You?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-office-provide-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-04 09:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Key Tips That Will Help You Create a Productive Work Environment</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/key-tips-that-will-help-you-create.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-19 16:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you want to grow your business, you need to have a productive work environment.

Some agents like to work from home, and that’s okay. Others like to have their office in an office. Here at RE/MAX Millennium, we offer both options. Either way, you’ll find a great work environment, and in our office, we have a cafe space, inviting decor, and a wonderful administrative team to support all our clients.

In any case, here are a couple tips to help you ensure a productive work environment.

“CREATE A PRODUCTIVE WORK ENVIRONMENT.”

If you work from home and that’s important to you, you should treat your workday just like you would anywhere else. If you’d wear a suit and tie to the office, wear a suit and tie at home. Dress how you’d normally dress, whether you have an appointment or not. Otherwise, you might find yourself sitting on the couch with a bag of Doritos watching TV when you should be prospecting.

It’s also important to have a regimented schedule when you work from home. If you have small children at home or you don’t have your own workspace there, you need to make sure you have a space in the office where you can actually get work done. Stay focused and don’t let yourself get distracted by emails or your smartphone (it’s not so “smart” if it’s distracting you).

Studies have shown that there’s no such thing as multitasking, so take 60- to 90-minute periods throughout the day to focus on one thing. I promise you that if you do this, your productivity will increase, and I have plenty of other productivity hacks that I’d be happy to share with you if you’re interested.

If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Rediscover the Lost Art of the Handwritten Note</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-rediscover-lost-art-of.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-28 12:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


With all modern methods of communication available today, like emails, texts, social media, and more, handwritten notes have become a lost art.

Think about it: When is the last time you received a personal, pen-and-paper letter?

Personally, I think reaching out this way is still important. This is why I spend some time each day to write five clients a personal note. Whether it’s an inquiry or simply a message of thanks—there is always a reason to send a handwritten note.

It’s been proven that writing three to five handwritten notes per day will boost your business. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve received a phone call from someone thanking me for taking this extra step in reaching out.

“WHETHER IT’S AN INQUIRY OR SIMPLY A MESSAGE OF THANKS—THERE IS ALWAYS A REASON TO SEND A HANDWRITTEN NOTE.”

Following this simple tip is an easy, inexpensive way to stay at the top of your clients’ minds, all while increasing the chances that they’ll send referral business your way.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Growing Your Business With Social Media</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-growing-your-business.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-01 13:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


With all of the different social media platforms out there, using them to grow your business can feel overwhelming. However, leveraging platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Snapchat, and Instagram (to name just a few), can be quite effective. The key is to be consistent.

Make sure that you are posting on a daily or weekly basis, and that your posts are appropriate. While it should mostly be business-related, you can also occasionally include personal touches. This way when people Google your name, they’ll be able to learn a little about you before meeting up with you for a listing appointment.

“WHILE IT SHOULD MOSTLY BE BUSINESS-RELATED, YOUR SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNTS CAN ALSO INCLUDE PERSONAL TOUCHES TO HELP POTENTIAL CLIENTS SEE YOU AS A REAL PERSON.”

If you want to keep your private Facebook life locked out, that is fine. That said, creating a Realtor Facebook page or business page will greatly benefit your business. And, if you’re comfortable doing so, adding in the personal things to your real estate page will help others see you as a real person.

Beyond posting, watch your clients and keep in touch with them to change an online situation into a personal situation. You can wish them a happy birthday or send them gifts when they have a new baby. This is especially important if they are someone who would refer you business. Taking these steps will help you build a long-term relationship.

Online interactions with clients can be turned into a source of referral business. The more you do this, the more you are going to win. Of course, you can buy internet leads, but I’m a fan of working by referral and building relationships with clients both online and off.

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me. I look forward to speaking with you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Which Leadership Philosophy Should You Use to Guide Your Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/which-leadership-philosophy-should-you.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-06 13:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I’d like to discuss an important concept: leading versus managing.

If you’ve ever been part of a team, you’ve almost certainly encountered one, or both, of these leadership styles. The way a team runs under each will be different, and noticeably so.

So what is the difference between these concepts?

First, managing means that the person in power is simply barking commands. Leading, on the other hand, is all about inspiring those who look to you for guidance.

Rather than simply telling people what to do, leading is all about guiding people toward the right decisions. This is the leadership approach that helps teams succeed.

“LEAD BY INSPIRATION, NOT BY ORDERS.”

For those of you who have a team or are interested in growing one, we would be happy to help you more fully understand how having the right leadership philosophy can benefit a collaborative environment.

Giving your team goals and allowing them to be part of the creative process will improve the results you see from their work. Your team members should feel as if you trust them, and as if they have the power to work autonomously toward the team’s larger objectives.

As a leader, your task is to educate, guide, and work alongside your team. Lead by inspiration, not by orders.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Our Core Values Mean to Us</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-our-core-values-mean-to-us.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-11 14:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I want to talk to you about core values. Every business owner should have a set of core values that drive the way they do business. Here are the core values we have at RE/MAX Millennium:

“WE EMBRACE SKILLS TRAINING, EDUCATION, AND PERSONAL GROWTH.”

• We always do what’s right, even when nobody’s looking.

• We put people first. People before profits.

• We hold people’s names sacred. We have a no-gossip policy here and we will not tolerate it.

• We’re always teachable and learning. That is why we really embrace skills training, education, and personal growth. We are one of only a few brokerages in town that does this type of program.

• We laugh and we have fun. We are all here to make money, but we have to have fun too.

• We are grateful.

• We are real and transparent. No facades here. You get what you see with us.

• We are one. We are all a team here at RE/MAX Millennium. Anybody in our office can help you and answer any questions at any time.

Those are our eight core values here and it is how we dictate our interactions with our team, our clients, and our community. If you have any questions about our core values or how to create your own, please feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Makes RE/MAX Millennium a Cut Above the Rest?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-makes-remax-millennium-cut-above.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-31 16:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4</guid>
        <description>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


There are many different things our team members cite as being their favorite aspect of RE/MAX Millennium. For some, it’s the teamwork-focused atmosphere, and for others, it’s great energy, or the knowledge that team leaders truly care about everyone’s success.

I’ve been selling real estate for nearly 15 years, but when I opened RE/MAX Millennium it became apparent that there were certain things I was ready to do differently. My team and I were able to redesign our office space and our core values around how we want to run business—which is essentially just an amplified version of what we were doing before.

So far, our team has loved what these changes have done for us and our clients. Broker associate Ron Mast, for example, has been in real estate and the mortgage industry for over 30 years, and he specifically chose to work with us at RE/MAX Millennium because of our great atmosphere.

And our clients love what’s going on at RE/MAX Millennium, too. According to team member and broker associate TJ Chambless, clients are always complimenting our office’s design and technological resources.

But our office isn’t all we’ve got going for us. Broker associate Jenny Daniels points to our team itself—our people—as being an invaluable resource to clients.

The list of benefits our team brings to the industry goes on and on. Broker associate Alan Daniels says our energy is one thing he personally values about working at RE/MAX Millennium. “It’s a great place to bounce ideas off of each other,” he says.

This sense of collaboration is so strong, in fact, that broker associate Marsha Meyer has said working for our team is like being part of a family. “Everyone really cares about making sure that I’m succeeding,” says Marsha.

“AGENTS HERE AT RE/MAX MILLENNIUM HAVE THE CHANCE TO GROW AS PROFESSIONALS, ALL WHILE DRAWING UPON THE EXPERIENCE OF OTHER SUCCESSFUL AGENTS ALL AROUND THEM.”

It’s easy to see that our RE/MAX Millennium team is a cut above the rest. So many of our agents have great things to say about what it’s like to work here, like broker associate Brian Daniels, who says that RE/MAX Millennium “offers more than the average RE/MAX brokerage.”

Specifically, one of the most significant things RE/MAX Millennium offers its agents is an emphasis on continued education, training, and support.

As for myself, I’m just grateful to be able to provide these opportunities for my team and our clients. Agents here at RE/MAX Millennium have the chance to grow as professionals, all while drawing upon the experience of other successful agents all around them.

At RE/MAX Millennium, we hold high ethical standards, provide high levels of support for our agents, and are always working to treat people right. So, if you’re thinking of making a career move, why not consider joining us? We’d love to show you where all this high praise comes from.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Hire a Real Estate Coach?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/schedule-free-business-consultation.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-11 14:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I want to let you in on what you should know before you hire a real estate coach.

First, do you even need a real estate coach? Even the greats like Tiger Woods and other major athletes have multiple coaches. Coaching is definitely a good way to help hold yourself accountable for your activities and to keep you in line with what’s happening in the current marketplace. With their help, you can understand how to navigate market trends and agent-client interactions.

The great thing about RE/MAX Millennium is that I offer coaching to any agents who want to come to my office. I will teach you and help you grow: I’ve coached with more than four other national coaches, and I even have a coach right now who I’m helping on a weekly basis.

I can share tips and tricks I’ve learned over the many years I’ve been in the real estate industry, working with professionals in prospecting, referrals, team-building, and more. I’ve spent hundreds of thousands of dollars on coaching, and I’m prepared to give you access to that pool of knowledge.

“I OFFER COACHING TO ANY AGENTS WHO WANT TO COME TO MY OFFICE.”

However, if you want to hire a coach, just be aware that it can be costly. Make sure you understand that it’s a time commitment; you might be on a weekly or monthly call or you might get homework assignments. If they’re good, your coach will hold you accountable.

You’ll also want to have a clear perspective on your goals. There are different types of coaches who specialize in different areas, so you’ll need to know what you want to learn from them and why before you select one to hire.

Finally, you’ll need to reach out and get testimonials from the coach’s clients, or else speak with agents who have worked with them, in order to make sure their process is legitimate and that they have successfully helped agents grow their business.

As a coaching expert, I’m happy to sit down with you and help you. If you have a question about a specific coach, I’ve done research on almost all of them, and I’d gladly share my thoughts with you. Please feel free to reach out to me by phone or email. I hope to hear from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Boost Your Productivity Using These 2 Tips</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/boost-your-productivity-using-these-2.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-04-19 13:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


There are a number of things you can do to increase your productivity without increasing the number of hours you spend working.

My first recommendation for boosting productivity is by implementing a tool called “Dominate Your Day”, or DYD. This tool prioritizes your day by listing the six most important dollar-producing activities you should be taking on. The tool also outlines your goals. If you’d like a copy of this, please let me know and I’d be happy to send you a copy.

“TIME BLOCKING IS THE GREATEST PRODUCTIVITY BOOSTER I CAN RECOMMEND.”

The second recommendation I have for increasing your productivity is carving out your calendar and implementing time blocking. This is a tip you’ve probably heard time and time again, but that’s because it works. Agents who time block can double or even triple their success. Time blocking is as simple as assigning specific tasks to specific hours of each day.

For example, my team and I have a huddle from 8:30 a.m. to 8:45 a.m. every single day. Of course, it’s also important to block off time for leisure, family, and vacation. I actually recommend blocking this time off first. Time blocking is the greatest productivity booster I can recommend.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can Texting Improve Your Conversion Rate?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-texting-improve-your-conversion.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-03-21 11:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Should you text your leads? Well, based on what we’ve found, our team and others are actually getting a far better response rate with texting than with calling.

Obviously, we like to call people when we first reach out since voice-to-voice contact still plays an important role. However, these days, most people let their phone go to voicemail.

You can call up to three times without leaving a message if you’re bold. They may answer if you are this persistent. But if they don’t, I recommend leaving a voicemail and also following up with a text message saying who you are and that you’d be happy to assist them with their real estate needs.

“IF YOU HAVEN’T BEEN DOING SO ALREADY, TEXT THOSE LEADS!”

There are text systems you can buy, but your phone is all you really need. If you haven’t been doing so already, text those leads! It will make a big difference in your conversation rate.

You can find samples of texts we’ve used to convert leads here, or here.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>6 Books That All Successful People Should Read</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/6-books-that-all-successful-people.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-08 10:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


One of the biggest sources of inspiration and motivation for me is the books that I’ve read. There are a number of books that I can point to that have helped me grow both professionally and personally. I believe that reading is a key to success, which is why I have a library for my team that is always growing. Here are a few of my favorite books that taught me countless lessons about real estate and business in general:

• “Think and Grow Rich” by Napoleon Hill
• “Millionaire Real Estate Agent” by Gary Keller
• “How to Win Friends and Influence People” by Dale Carnegie
• “The E-Myth” by Michael Gerber
• “Eat That Frog!” by Brian Tracy
• “Fanatical Prospecting” by Jeb Blount

Reading these books will help you take your business and transform it into a career and a lifestyle that will help you build the life you want. These are just a handful at the ones at the top of my list, so if you have any suggestions, I’d love to hear them. If you have any other questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jason Daniels</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jason Daniels</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
