<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Colorado Springs Real Estate Podcast with Jason Daniels</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jason Daniels</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-03-31 16:10:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jason Daniels</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>info@jasondanielshomes.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jason Daniels</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Colorado Springs Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Properly Prepare for a Buyer’s Appointment</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-properly-prepare-for-a-buyers-appointment.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-20 09:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today I’m going to show you how to properly prepare for a buyer’s appointment. I encourage you to have the buyer meet you in your office to show their level of commitment to working with you. If your office is a bit of a long commute, you can meet at a coffee shop or other neutral location that’s closer to them. Keep in mind that safety is of the utmost importance here. Make sure you have materials that show the agent why they should work with you and do a little research about the buyer themself. To learn more, watch this short video.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Advice for Reaching Out to Home Value Report Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/advice-for-reaching-out-to-home-value-report-leads.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-20 09:00:41 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I wanted to quickly reach out to talk to you about the follow-up process for a home value report. Most of these websites will send out an automated report, but sometimes it will just be an email to you with the information. You definitely want to follow up immediately and treat them like a normal internet lead. Thank them for registering for your website, let them know about their automated value report, and that you can come out to do an analysis for a more detailed evaluation. To learn more about the process and some best practices, watch this short video.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Knowing What Type of Content to Share</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/knowing-what-type-of-content-to-share.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-10 16:52:53 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Not all content is good content. Today I&rsquo;m sharing how to know the difference and better engage with your sphere.

 

As a real estate agent, we must engage with our sphere regularly. The challenge with that, of course, is crafting meaningful content that provides your clients with value. Here are some tips for content creation: 

Educate your audience about the housing market, real estate, and upcoming listings. Highlight interesting trends in the housing market and offer expert analysis and predictions. We don’t want to just repeatedly send them listings—they can look for those elsewhere. While it’s important to occasionally send them listings so that they know you’re actively involved in the business, adding the extra touch of, say, a video blog or an interesting social media post can be impactful. 

“Don’t overrun your personal social media page with business.”

Obviously, whatever you send through—whether via postcards in the U.S. mail or newsletters via email—should be carefully thought out. There’s an infamous story about an agent who sent out recipe cards for 10 years, only to find out that someone in their sphere all along chose a different Realtor for their home sale. When confronted, the person told this agent, “Oops, I forgot you were a Realtor. I thought you were involved with some cooking school.” 

That story illustrates the importance of keeping your content industry-related. On your personal social media accounts, follow this general rule: Make one business post for every three to four personal posts. Don’t overrun your personal page with business, as it will likely annoy your friends and potential clients. 

Buyers and sellers, millennials especially, want to see that you’re a real person and not some scam; you need to be active on the most popular social media platforms. On them, you can highlight local businesses or plug upcoming client events. Truly, there’s no limit to the amount of valuable information you can share with your sphere. 

Please reach out via phone, email, or the links below. I’d be happy to talk with you about how to best contact your sphere and strengthen your business relationships. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Not all content is good content. Today I’m sharing how to know the difference and better engage with your sphere.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Not all content is good content. Today I’m sharing how to know the difference and better engage with your sphere.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Quick Tips to Boost Your Referral Business</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/quick-tips-to-boost-your-referral-business.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-24 11:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How do you ask for referrals? Today I&rsquo;ll share my tips and best practices.

 

If you’re reluctant to ask for more referrals, there are a few simple things you can try to increase your referral business.

First, have a conversation with your friends and family. Ask if they know anyone interested in buying or selling property.  If they do, do they have a Realtor to help them? This way, you’re letting them know that you’re looking for referrals, which might be easier to get from a trusted source.

You can also ask past clients for referrals. It’s important to let them know at the very beginning of the transaction that you work by referral and remind them through the process. To increase the frequency with which you can get referrals from past clients, make sure their experience is superior. 

“Be sure to reach out consistently throughout the process.”

Research shows when someone is looking for a specific thing, like a car, they’ll start to see it everywhere. Similarly, when someone is shopping for a home, their ears are always open for conversations about real estate, be it at work, church, or wherever. 

Transactions can take anywhere from 30 to 90 days, so be sure to reach out consistently throughout the process. I can’t tell you how much that has helped my business grow. Other things, like handwritten notes and even housecalls, can help you get referrals, as well.

If you have any questions about getting more referrals, we offer training courses here at RE/MAX Millennium. Feel free to reach out to us to schedule a consultation or to address any other questions you have.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How do you ask for referrals? Today I’ll share my tips and best practices.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How do you ask for referrals? Today I’ll share my tips and best practices.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Do You Increase Your Odds of Getting a Review?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-do-you-increase-your-odds-of-getting-a-review.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-07 08:54:44 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here are a few quick tips that will help you get more reviews.

 

We all know that with the advent of social media and the rise of sites like Yelp and Zillow, reviews have become increasingly important to real estate agents. What’s the key to getting more, better reviews, though?

First, you need to provide the best customer service possible. This is an obvious tip, but you need to be professional and follow up with people. The very first time you meet with them, tell them you appreciate their time and that you’ll be asking for a review toward the end of the process. I know you like to get reviews on different platforms, but I recommend picking just two or three of them. In addition to Zillow and Yelp, Google and Facebook are good options. 

We’ve found that if you ask them for a review right before closing (not at closing—that should be about them), they’re more willing to give you one. If you ask for one after the closing, it might be a while before you get one because at that point they’re more concerned with unpacking and settling into their new home. 

“You need to be professional and follow up with people.”

Another good way to get reviews is to hold a contest centered around them. You can’t just ask for a five-star review—federal law prohibits that—but you can offer prizes like an overnight hotel stay or an iPad for any past clients who write you a review. All you have to do is send out a video just like this one where you thank them for their business and ask them for honest reviews on the platforms you’ve already picked. You’d be surprised at how many you can get. Before you do this, though, check with your broker to make sure you’re not breaking any federal or state laws. 

The next time you host a client party, you can also ask past clients to write a review before they attend. 

These are just a few ideas to keep in mind, but if you’d like to talk more about this subject, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to schedule a consultation with you and do everything I can to help generate the best reviews possible. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are a few quick tips that will help you get more reviews.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are a few quick tips that will help you get more reviews.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Using a Dialer</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/using-a-dialer.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-12-23 14:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Videos/Using+a+Dialer.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Whether or not you should use a dialer depends on the marketing you do.&nbsp;

Should you use a dialer? 

In case you don’t know, a dialer is a system that automatically dials lists for you. It helps you be more efficient, and most of them have a built-in CRM, as well, so you can track notes. If you want to get really fancy, you can buy a triple-line dialer that can call three people at a time. 

In any case, whether you should use a dialer or not depends on the type of marketing you do. If you’re just reaching out to your sphere and checking in with them, you don’t really need one. It might help if you have 300 or 400 clients and you need to call all of them for a single event, though. 

“Dialers are typically meant for circle prospecting and cold calling.”

Otherwise, dialers are typically meant for circle prospecting and cold calling—any scenario that involves reaching out to a large volume of people. The system I like to use is called Mojo Dialer, but I’ve also used the RedX Storm® Dialer.

If you’d like to know more about specific dialers my team and I use, and how we use them, give me a call. They’re a handy tool to have to make your business more efficient. If you don’t need to make a lot of large dials, though, you’ll be fine focusing on your sphere by just picking up your phone the old-fashioned way. 

As always, if you have questions about any other topic, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to help you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Videos/Using+a+Dialer.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Videos/Using+a+Dialer.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Whether or not you should use a dialer depends on the marketing you do.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Whether or not you should use a dialer depends on the marketing you do.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Value of Scripts</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-value-of-scripts.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-12-17 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

It&rsquo;s important to learn scripts as an agent, but you shouldn&rsquo;t sound robotic when using them.

 

As an agent, you absolutely should use scripts when dealing with clients, but you shouldn’t sound canned when using them. 

It’s important to learn scripts because real estate boils down to a couple of different buying and selling processes, and the average consumer will have the same questions and objections depending on whether they’re buying or selling. 

Once in a while, you’ll get a question or objection you’ve never dealt with, but most agents develop scripts and dialogues to address the majority of their clients’ concerns. It’s our professional duty to focus on understanding our clients’ needs, and by learning scripts, we can listen to their needs when they’re talking to us instead of trying to think of what to say next. 

“If you’re able to answer your clients’ objections professionally they’ll know that you know what you’re talking about.”

If you’d like to see some of the scripts my team and I use, use this link to schedule a consultation. We practice our scripts daily, and we have different scripts for all types of clients and objections. Like I said, you don’t want to sound canned, which is why I advise that you keep the key elements of the script the same, but alter your responses so they feel like they’re coming from you.

If you’re able to answer your clients’ objections professionally they’ll know that you know what you’re talking about. By sounding more professional, you’ll have more success converting your clients. 

If you have more questions about the value of scripts or you have any other real estate needs at all, feel free to call or email me. I’d love to speak with you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>It’s important to learn scripts as an agent, but you shouldn’t sound robotic when using them.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>It’s important to learn scripts as an agent, but you shouldn’t sound robotic when using them.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Contact Expired Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-contact-expired-leads.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-12-03 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today&rsquo;s message is about how to prospect expired leads.

 

Today I want to discuss how to go about prospecting expired leads. If you don’t have a large sphere of clients, going after expired listings is one of the lowest-hanging fruits you can grab at. The basic method of getting expired listings is consistent followups. The number one way real estate agents get in touch with expired listings is by simply calling them. 

“Whatever you do, you need to be consistent.”

There are multiple services out there like REDX or Vulcan7 that you can subscribe to for a fairly affordable rate, and they’ll deliver to you, through their site or your email, expired listings from that day. You can also go back and see past expired listings to call. There are different methods you can employ, but that first day you should reach out three to five times by phone. The second approach is mailing postcards or letters. 

There are different systems, coaches, and so on you can buy, but find one that works for you. Whatever you do, you need to be consistent. Don’t just call them the day the listing expires, you want to follow up every day or every other day with a text, call, or email. You can find out more information about them by just looking on Facebook. We call that research, it’s not stalking. Do your homework. 

The most aggressive way that I’ve heard of is literally going and knocking on the door. Devise an explanation of how you’re great at selling homes that didn’t sell the first time and create a pre-listing package. Frequently my team and I are the second or third Realtors people come to, and we share our success stories with them of how we were able to sell former clients’ homes for full price in 30 days when it was expired once or twice before. Share how you’re different from their last Realtor and can be trusted. Show them your value. They don’t necessarily need to know how many homes you’ve sold, they want to know you care and that you’re going to be there for them and not leave them hanging like their previous Realtor. 

Feel free to pick up the phone and call or stop by the office and I can show you what we do to find expired leads. Also, reach out by phone or email with questions or go to our website and schedule a consultation. I’d love to meet with you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today’s message is about how to prospect expired leads.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today’s message is about how to prospect expired leads.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Content Should You Send Your Farm?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-content-should-you-send-your-farm.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-18 12:53:12 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

The content you send your farm shouldn&rsquo;t be exactly the same as the content you send your sphere. Let&rsquo;s talk about why.

 

When you send out content to your farm, the information you send them should be a little different from the things you send your sphere, in general. This is because farms are restricted to a geographic area, whereas your sphere is just a collection of people you’ve connected with. 

Therefore, the content you send your farm should be a reflection of where they live. This might mean sending out a newsletter detailing area sales activity, video market updates, or notices about local events. 

“The content you send your farm should be a reflection of where they live.”

People tend to be most interested in content that relates to their neighborhood, which can work to your advantage as an agent if you happen to have any listings in the area. If you’re able to secure email addresses from people within your farm, giving them email invites to open houses is another great idea. 

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The content you send your farm shouldn’t be exactly the same as the content you send your sphere. Let’s talk about why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The content you send your farm shouldn’t be exactly the same as the content you send your sphere. Let’s talk about why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Many Touches Should You Have With Your Farm?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-many-touches-should-you-have-with-your-farm.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-04 13:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How many touches should you have with your farm? Here are my thoughts.

 

Here’s a question for you agents out there: When it comes to your farm, how many touches should you have?

With your sphere of influence, we always encourage you to have 30 or more contacts a year between calls, emails, newsletters, postcards, etc.

“Send out something in the physical mail once a month, or once a quarter at a minimum.”

For your geographical farm, however, it’s great to have at least 18 to 24 touches. Depending on the size of the farm, it might be more feasible to do more or less. If you’re just starting a farm that includes between 50 and 300 people, you’ll probably want to have more contacts. If you’re farming a wider area, you may not be able to have as many contacts with your base.

Here’s what I recommend: Send out something in the physical mail once a month, or once a quarter at a minimum, and if you have the phone numbers from your farm, try getting in touch with each person four times a year. You could also try walking through the neighborhood to do some door-knocking; this will also help you get to know the community.

If you have any questions about the specific content that we send out to our farms or anything else related to keeping in touch with your farm, don’t hesitate to reach out to us for a consultation. We’d be happy to talk to you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How many touches should you have with your farm? Here are my thoughts.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How many touches should you have with your farm? Here are my thoughts.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>To Go Wide or Deep When Farming in Real Estate</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/to-go-wide-or-deep-when-farming-in-real-estate.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-21 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Farming is an effective lead-generation strategy, but there is more than one way to do it. Here are two of the most common.

 

When you’re farming an area, is it better to go wide or deep into that area? With most agents, I find that it’s better to start by going deep with a small farm and building out from there.  If you have more time than money, it makes sense to go deeper instead of wider at first.

It could be a neighborhood you live in, where your office is, or where your kids go to school. Pick an area with anywhere from 50 to 300 homes. You can knock on doors, hand out brochures, and make a connection with the community.

If you already have a presence in your farm and have the money to spend on marketing, you have the luxury of going wide. You can farm a much larger area of thousands of homes by going wide.

“Start by picking an area with 50 to 300 homes.”

The key focus should be on your budget and your goal. If you go wide, you can’t go as deep if you don’t have a large team helping you. That’s why I encourage going small and deep at first, then start going wider once you know the community better.

If you have any questions for me about farming or the real estate business in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Farming is an effective lead-generation strategy, but there is more than one way to do it. Here are two of the most common.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Farming is an effective lead-generation strategy, but there is more than one way to do it. Here are two of the most common.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Is the Purpose of Circle Prospecting?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-is-the-purpose-of-circle-prospecting.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-13 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Agents often ask me what the purpose of circle prospecting is, so let’s get to the bottom of this common question today.

Before we get to this, though, allow me to quickly define circle prospecting for those who may not know.

Circle prospecting is essentially a method of contacting potential leads by reaching out to people within a certain mile radius around a particular home. One of the most common ways to do this is by purchasing and calling reverse directories.

“All in all, circle prospecting is a fantastic technique all agents should utilize.”

Now that we’ve covered what circle prospecting is, let’s move on to what its purpose is. There are actually many different reasons an agent might use circle prospecting. You may use it to advertise open houses, let buyers know about local listings, or to see if anyone in a given area is interested in selling their home.

The bottom line is that circle prospecting brings you business. Circle prospecting will mostly bring you sellers, but it can bring in buyers, as well. All in all, it’s a fantastic technique all agents should utilize.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What is circle prospecting and why should agents use it? Let’s discuss.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What is circle prospecting and why should agents use it? Let’s discuss.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Generate More Traffic for Your Open House</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-generate-more-traffic-for-your-open-house.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-09-23 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How do you market your open house to generate more traffic?

There are a lot of ways to advertise an open house, but the days of just placing an ad in the newspaper and putting up a few signs are over. With that in mind, I want to share with you the steps my team and I take for all our open houses that always generate a lot of traffic.

First, you must advertise your home online. There are a lot of websites (Zillow, Realtor.com, etc.) that allow you to do this, in addition to the local MLS. Also, whenever we do an open house, we email every agent who has sold a home in that ZIP code and invite them and their clients to attend. Additionally, we use paid advertisements for the property on Facebook.

“The days of just placing an ad in the newspaper and putting up a few signs are over.”

After that, we call residents in the surrounding neighborhood and invite them over. If we have time, we’ll knock on the doors of the same houses we’re calling and hand these people a personalized invitation.

Sometimes, we’ll host a private open house for neighbors only, which allows our agents to meet with them before the general public is invited. The people who attend this pre-open house might be thinking about selling themselves and are on the lookout for a good agent, so not only are you attracting traffic to your current listing, but you’re also attracting other future seller clients.

If you have any more questions about how to generate traffic for your open house, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Want to generate more traffic to your open house? Here’s how.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Want to generate more traffic to your open house? Here’s how.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Tracking Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-tracking-leads.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-09-12 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Regardless of the industry, every business owner should track where their revenue comes from, and real estate agents are no different. You have probably heard this before, but you truly need to be tracking your leads.

Why? 

The bottom line is that tracking your leads helps you to make sure that you’re spending your money and your time wisely. All you need is a simple spreadsheet to determine where your clients are coming from. If you identify that most of your clients tend to come from a certain source, you can then redirect your time, money, and energy accordingly.

“It’s all about finding what makes sense for you and your business.”

If you’re tracking your leads and leveraging your resources correctly, you should be making at least twice as much as you’re spending. If something isn’t bringing you a high return (or any return at all), then it may be time to scratch it off of your schedule. 

Once you get the hang of tracking your leads, you may find it beneficial to invest in CRM software that will do it for you. It’s all about finding what makes sense for you and your business. 

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Running a successful real estate business becomes much easier when you know where your revenue is coming from, and today we’ll explain how tracking your leads can help you do just that.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Running a successful real estate business becomes much easier when you know where your revenue is coming from, and today we’ll explain how tracking your leads can help you do just that.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips to Improve Your Listing Presentation</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-improve-your-listing-presentation.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-23 11:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

First, the key to differentiating yourself in our marketplace is providing a pre-listing packet you either have delivered or deliver yourself to the seller before the meeting. In my packets, I provide information that details the benefits of hiring me and what they can expect when working with me. This way, they have most of their questions already answered before we meet face to face and we can get down to business and get the listing agreement signed. 

“If you haven’t already, put together a pre-listing packet you can give to buyers that outlines the benefits of working with you.”

So if you haven’t already, put together a pre-listing packet you can give to buyers that outlines the benefits of working with you. Don’t talk about why you’re the top agent in the area or ramble about how many homes you’ve sold—stick to what kind of value you provide them. 

Second, be on time. If you show up just five minutes late to an appointment, you’re in trouble. I recommend showing up at least five to 10 minutes early and then, at the agreed-upon time, knocking on the door and introducing yourself. If the seller is speaking to other agents, there’s a chance some of them will be late to their appointments, so they’ll be impressed with your punctuality. 

Lastly, don’t spend too much time in the seller’s home unless they have a lot of questions. Some agents like to spend half a day in their would-be client’s home, but they’re not planning on you spending a half-day there. Keep things professional, build a rapport, and ask for a tour of the home so you get a chance to connect with them about something. If you find a connection point, don’t focus on it, because that will distract from the reason you’re there in the first place.

If you’d like to talk more about improving your listing presentation, don’t hesitate to give me a call or schedule a consultation. I’d be happy to speak with you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>If you want to improve your listing presentation and sell more homes, here are a few quick tips to keep in mind.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If you want to improve your listing presentation and sell more homes, here are a few quick tips to keep in mind.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Top 4 Sources for Listing Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-top-4-sources-for-listing-leads.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-12 11:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What are the best sources for listing leads? Find out today.

 

There are many different places an agent can find business, but when it comes to finding listing leads, these four sources stand out above the rest:

1. Your sphere of influence. Staying in touch with your sphere of influence is incredibly powerful. You must always let them know that you’re never too busy to take on their real estate needs, or their referrals.

2. Your professional network. Over time, real estate professionals build a lot of relationships with fellow Realtors from all over the country. By maintaining these relationships, you’re likely to attract referrals from agents who have been approached by clients looking to buy or sell outside of their market. This is especially effective in areas with military bases, which attract a large number of out-of-state families.

“The demand for professional help in the real estate industry has never been higher.”

3. FSBO sellers. People who are interested in selling their property on their own generally end up needing more help than they expected. Studies show that more people have turned to Realtors for professional help than was true during any given year over the last decade. Although listing online has become easier for sellers to manage on their own, the rest of the home selling process has become more complex. The demand for professional help in the real estate industry has never been higher.

4. People who have previously failed to sell. The biggest mistake someone who has failed to sell in the past can make is to try the same approach again. Working with a new agent (like you) will be in their best interest, and if you can convince them of this, you’ll find that this demographic of sellers is an incredible source of leads.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What are the best sources for listing leads? Find out today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What are the best sources for listing leads? Find out today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Does It Take to Become a Successful Entrepreneur?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-does-it-take-to-become-a-successful-entrepreneur.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-29 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

A few tips for new or aspiring entrepreneurs.

 

What does it take to become a successful entrepreneur? I’m often asked this question by fledgling business owners, and it’s no wonder: Entrepreneurship comes with its fair share of risks. Because of that, developing good habits and practices right from the word go is very important.

Above all, success in your entrepreneurial pursuits depends on your determination. You need to make sure you’re determined to achieve the goals you set out to achieve. More than just fame or fortune, it’s about your value proposition. If the value of what you’re selling goes above and beyond what people are paying for it, you’re sure to succeed.

In one of my previous videos, I discussed the importance of being an early riser and sticking to a morning routine, which is a key ingredient in your success as an entrepreneur as well. If you missed it, you can check it out here.

“If the value of what you’re selling goes above and beyond what people are paying for it, you’re sure to succeed.”

In addition, I’d recommend reading the book “Traction: Get a Grip on Your Business” by Gino Wickman. In it, he provides a blueprint for strategic planning and setting quarterly “rocks” or goals. Whether you’re just now getting your business off the ground or you want to take it to the next level, reading this book will help you map out where you want to go.

Your focus will also be instrumental to your success. The more you focus on fine-tuning your sales and marketing, the more your focus will expand to not only reach the people who know, like, and trust you, but to create new lines of communication with people in the marketplace.

You’re probably wondering how many hours a week you’ll have to dedicate. It’s important to discipline yourself to treat entrepreneurship as a job. When you’re first starting out, you can probably expect to work 10 to 12 hours a day, six or seven days a week. Eventually, you’ll need to return to a healthy work-life balance, but in the short term, being an entrepreneur will demand your undivided attention and a lot of time, energy, and effort.

If you have any questions about today’s topic or you’d like to schedule a one-on-one consultation, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I look forward to speaking with you!   
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>A few tips for new or aspiring entrepreneurs</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>A few tips for new or aspiring entrepreneurs</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Convert Internet Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-convert-internet-leads.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-09 10:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Having a follow-up strategy in place is key to converting internet leads.

 

What is your plan for converting internet leads? The answer boils down to three factors: your immediate, mid-term, and long-term follow up. 

Statistics say that the average buyer starts looking at homes online two years before they’re actually ready to buy. Here in the Colorado Springs area, the average is closer to six to 12 months, but we still have some buyers who need to buy sooner than that (i.e., within the next 30 to 60 days).

How does our team handle these types of leads?

Let’s start with our immediate follow-up. In this case, we reach out to someone within five to 10 minutes of registering on our website. Whether it’s an ISA or an agent, they’ll call between three to five times that day without leaving a voicemail. If you leave a voicemail, the potential buyer may tag your number and block it, or just never call you back. We try and spread out these phone calls throughout the day.

“Your goal should be consistent follow up—the leads work when you work.”

We also follow up via text and email—a lot of clients that we’re able to convert started with a text message conversation. I won’t say whether this is a generational trend, but a lot of people prefer to respond to a text than a call.

Our mid-term follow up is for buyers who, once we make contact with them, indicate that they’re ready to buy within 60 to 90 days. In the meantime, we reach out to them about once a week and build up our rapport.

Our long-term follow up is for buyers who want to buy after 90 days, and we typically reach out to them twice a month with a text or email.

It’s best to have a CRM in place to track these leads, and there are dozens of good ones out there that you can choose from. Your goal should be consistent follow up—the leads work when you work.

If you have any questions about this topic or need help with your follow-up strategy, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Having a follow-up strategy in place is key to converting internet leads. What is your plan for converti</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Having a follow-up strategy in place is key to converting internet leads. What is your plan for converti</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Does It Take to Be a Successful Entrepreneur?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-does-it-take-to-be-a-successful-entrepreneur.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-21 14:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+Does+It+Require+to+Be+a+Successful+Entrepreneur_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I meet up-and-coming business owners all the time and they sometimes ask me what it takes to be a successful entrepreneur. I’d like to share my thoughts with all of you today.

Basically, it all boils down to determination. You have to make sure that you’re determined to achieve the goals you want. It’s not all about the money or the fame; it’s about serving others. If you can provide a value for someone that’s higher than what they’re already paying for, then you’re going to be a true success.

It takes a lot of grit— you have to grind every single day, starting by forming a strong morning routine. Learn more about that here in a recent video we did.

Another lesson I take with me is from the book “Traction” by Gino Wickman. In a nutshell, it talks about being successful in a strategic way. You have to make quarterly goals to move your business forward and if you don’t, things will remain stagnant.

“It takes a lot of grit and you have to grind daily.”

For real estate, you need to make sure you’re contacting clients, people who know you, and new people. Consistency is key, though, and you need to dedicate a lot of time to perfecting the process. 

I like to tell people that I’m part-time, I just have to pick the 12 hours a day I’m going to work. Of course, that’s a little tongue-in-cheek, but there is some truth to it. To get things off the ground floor, you’ll have to put in long hours, but if you do and you stay focused, you’ll be able to greatly reduce that time because working that much simply isn’t good for you or your family.

If you have any questions for me about what it takes to be a successful entrepreneur or anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+Does+It+Require+to+Be+a+Successful+Entrepreneur_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+Does+It+Require+to+Be+a+Successful+Entrepreneur_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Being a successful entrepreneur isn’t all about money. This is what it truly takes.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Being a successful entrepreneur isn’t all about money. This is what it truly takes.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Effectively Advertise Open Houses</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-effectively-advertise-open-houses.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-18 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+to+Effectively+Advertise+Open+Houses.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How many signs should you put out for an open house, and how do you get people to register? You want to get as much traffic as you can into your open house, and today we’ll be talking about how to do it. 

Typically, we put out between 20 and 30 signs for an open house. If you can find a shopping center with a grocery store as its central hub, put signs leading from there to the open house. This can nearly double your traffic. 

We have metal A-frame signs as well as corrugated plastic signs, which are much more affordable. Keep in mind that you’ll likely lose some signs; cars may run them over, kids could take them, etc.

“If you can find a shopping center with a grocery store as its central hub, put signs leading from there to the open house.”

Place your signs strategically in busy intersections; it also helps to put multiple signs before a turn. This way, people simply can’t miss it. 

At the open house itself, I set up a table where people can register. I have a bowl where people can enter to win prizes, and we ask for their name, phone number, email, and address. We also say that this is for security purposes, as the seller wants to know who is entering their home. 

Have a team present so someone can cover the table while others can show people the home and ensure visitors are acting appropriately. 

These tips should help you make the most out of your open houses. If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+to+Effectively+Advertise+Open+Houses.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+to+Effectively+Advertise+Open+Houses.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Effectively advertising your open house is a great way to find potential buyers. Here’s how to do it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Effectively advertising your open house is a great way to find potential buyers. Here’s how to do it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Key to Success Is Staying Focused</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-key-to-success-is-staying-focused.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-24 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We’ve found that with all these new tech toys and social media platforms, there are so many distractions in the world of real estate.

To help hone their focus, I have our agents sit down and write out the top three areas they want to focus on in their business. Once they figure out what they want to do, whether it be FSBOs, expireds, internet leads, or working by referral, we challenge them to divert their focus to those three areas. If they’re a new agent, we ask them to pick three pillars of business that they think they’d like.

We have different advanced courses where we can break up the year, but concentrating on three areas is a good way of keeping things simple.

But what does it mean to focus?

For our part, my team likes to come into the office, get their things ready, do a quick team huddle to see how things are going, and then do a little bit of script and role-play practice.

“Focusing on new business and new client acquisition are both key to maintaining success.”

From 9 a.m. to 11 a.m. Monday to Friday, also called our “power hour,” our focus is on the phones, where we call our internet leads and personal spheres to work referrals. During that time, we also write handwritten notes to thank our clients and those who are referred to us.

After the power hour, we go over scripts and role playing again, just to see how things went.

From there on out, the agents go off to do whatever they need for the rest of the day—listing appointments, buyer appointments, inspections, and so on. 

The great thing about this system is that by the time our agents are free to go out and complete their tasks, they’ll already have done the most important thing of the day, which is focusing on new business and new client acquisition. Both are key to maintaining success.

If you have any questions about focusing on what matters the most in our business, feel free to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Let’s talk about focus.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Let’s talk about focus.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Become a Top Producer Like Me?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-become-top-producer-like-me.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-11 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


I got my start in real estate back in 2003, when I had just moved back to Colorado Springs and didn’t have a lot of prospects. Through grit, determination, and the help of my mentor and father, Brian Daniels, I learned the ropes.

My father told me that he wouldn’t give me a business, but would instead make me earn it. The interesting thing was that everyone he knew was already on his list of clients, meaning that I’d have to create a whole new sphere of influence.

When I started out selling homes, I was working mostly through referrals, making calls, writing notes, pop-bys, and expanding my sphere. I would ask the people I contacted “If you had a family member or friend who was going to buy a home, do you have a Realtor you would refer to them?” That way, I could avoid asking them directly if they were planning to sell their home—doing that on a regular basis might have inclined them to start avoiding my calls and emails.

Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there. I would decide how many homes I wanted to sell, come up with a gameplan, and set myself to work every morning and afternoon answering calls and emails.

To be a top producer, it takes a couple things beyond just grit, determination, and professionalism. I recommend those who want to become high-level agents in the industry to get their education. I don’t just mean the continuing education that the state requires, but also diving in deep to learn more about the industry. Classes are available at title companies and seminars for you to delve into certain topics to enhance your business.

“Building my business came down to setting goals and then working backward from there.”

Additionally, once it’s within your budget, you might consider traveling to other areas of the country for conferences, networking, and coaching from other top producers around the nation. I’ve had many different coaches throughout the years, and I definitely recommend serious agents find their own mentors to learn from their knowledge and expertise.

Doing this myself, I’ve managed to build up an agent network from which I get referrals. It’s also how I started to build my own team, which allowed us to do more expansive marketing campaigns to garner more leads.

To be a top producer in Colorado Springs, you also need to learn how to play nicely with others. Yes, we do represent our clients’ best interests, but there’s a certain way that high-level agents need to handle themselves during transactions. When we work peer-to-peer and Realtor-to-Realtor, we want to maintain a professional relationship. The MLS is, after all, a cooperative resource that is best utilized when we all work well together.

Ultimately, if you make goals, find a mentor or coach, work hard, start with people you know to build your database, and continue in that fashion, you can become a top producer in the field.

If you have any questions or need any advice about how to advance your own career as an agent, please feel free to reach out to me. Indeed, that’s why I started this brokerage: I wanted to help more agents reach their goals.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+How+Can+You+Become+a+Top+Producer+Like+Me_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How does one become a top producer in Colorado Springs? Today I’ll share my own story.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Client Events Are a Great Tool for Agents</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/events-are-perfect-for-bringing.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-31 15:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


I hear this question a lot from my fellow agents: Should I hold client events?

Absolutely! If you want to grow your referral base, these events are crucial. We do four major events each year, but you don’t need a huge budget to host something great. Starting out with a simple happy hour gathering for your best clients can be a great way to test the waters. Then, you can focus on bigger, better events for your entire client list.

Here are some of the things we like to do:

A chocolate giveaway in February alongside a party in our office
A family-friendly night at the movies in June where we rent out multiple theaters
A barbecue extravaganza in August where we go all out with big giveaways, plenty of food, and fun for all
A pie giveaway around Thanksgiving

“You don’t need a huge budget to host something great.”

It’s always good to have small get-togethers to supplement these big events. Take your biggest clients and go golfing, attend a sporting event, etc. Don’t overspend, and absolutely do not forget to follow up after these events. Thank them for coming, share pictures of the event, and so on.

If you have any questions or need further information about making your business more successful, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to helping you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Why+Client+Events+Are+a+Great+Tool+for+Agents.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Events are perfect for bringing together your clients, and there are many effective ones you can consider.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>4 Best Sources for Listing Leads</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/4-best-sources-for-listing-leads.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-14 12:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I’m excited to talk about some of the top sources for listing leads. Here’s my list for all of the other agents out there:

1. Sphere and past clients. I can’t stress this enough. Embrace and engage with your sphere and past clients. When you talk to them, make sure they know you’re never too busy for their referrals.

2. A network of agents. 10 years ago, this was a lot harder to do because you had to do it in person. With the advent of social media, it’s much easier. I do recommend meeting people in person when you can, but it really makes sense to reach out to agents in communities where military homebuyers are coming into Colorado Springs. Do your research and start finding these Realtors on Facebook and LinkedIn.

3+4. FSBO/Expired. A lot of people don’t like working these lists, but they should. These are two groups of people who you already know want to sell their home. In the last year, we’ve seen more people using a Realtor than in the previous 10+ years. Things are getting a little bit more complicated in terms of marketing, so these types of home sellers want expert advice. Nine times out of 10, I find that expired listings happen because of the previous agent’s error. The key is to pick one strategy and stick to it. Don’t get distracted by shiny objects. Just find a system and stick to it.

“Building a network of agents is much easier these days.”

If you have any questions about any of these strategies or anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email today. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+4+Best+Sources+for+Listing+Leads.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Finding great listing leads isn’t as hard as you think. These are the four best sources you should know about.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Many Benefits My Brokerage Provides to Agents</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/as-broker-owner-of-remax-millennium-i.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-17 13:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


What value can our brokerage provide you?

We have the best value given our fees here at RE/MAX. In fact, the average agent here in Colorado Springs sells about 6 homes per year, but our agents sell over 26 homes per year on average.

There’s a reason for that: One of the No. 1 things we focus on here is training, which is covered for you. We do weekly and monthly trainings, though none of it is mandatory if you don’t want to participate.

We also strive to keep things fresh and new. Other brokerages in town rehash the same materials over and over.

RE/MAX Millennium makes an active effort to be on the cutting-edge technology, which is critical for your success, especially with the way the market is shifting.

“We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.”

On top of that, we have administrative staff who help you from the front end by greeting your clients, as well as the back end, where they take care of all your paperwork and ensure that you’re compliant with laws and procedures. We’re willing to hold your hand as much or as little as you like throughout the process.

Finally, we have, hands down, the nicest office. This is not me boasting—I have been told this by many people. We even have an open cafe space where our agents can hang out together with clients. We also host our client appreciation events and parties right here in the office.

Our brokerage prides itself on building a community in which our agents know that they’ll help each other out. In fact, among our core values as a company are transparency and willingness to help others.

These are just a few snippets of the values and benefits you stand to gain by working with us here at RE/MAX Millennium. If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us here. I’d be happy to have a conversation with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

As the broker owner of RE/MAX Millennium, I would like to share with you the benefits of working with us as a broker/owner.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Another Successful Event for Colorado Springs Business Owners</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/another-successful-event-for-colorado.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-27 11:02:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit, and it was a resounding success. I started promoting it because I wanted to bring together small businesses and put on a great event with a national speaker without having to drive to Denver. Through technology, marketing, and networking, we all learned a lot about what it takes to grow your business in today’s economic climate. We’re so happy that so many of you were able to join us.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We recently held our Peak Mastermind Summit here in Colorado Springs and had a fantastic time. We hope all of you who joined us did as well.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Buyers Agents vs. Listing Agents: What Should a New Real Estate Professional Become?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/buyers-agents-vs-listing-agents-what.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-21 12:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


People just entering the real estate industry may wonder what role within the profession would be best for them. Actually, the best way to answer this question is by asking yourself a couple of others. For example: Do you want to be on a team? If so, becoming a buyer’s agent or a listing agent may be a good option. Being a listing agent will allow you to leverage your time, money, and efforts more quickly, but most agents start out working with buyers. If you’d like to learn more or have any other questions, we would be happy to schedule an appointment and talk about this topic in greater depth.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

What role should you fill when you get started in real estate?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Most Effective Way to Become a Licensed Realtor</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-most-effective-way-to-become.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-08 11:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you’re wanting to get into the real estate business, there are a few options you have when you’re first starting out. Today, we’ll be discussing the ways you can begin your career as a Realtor.

To earn your license, you’ll typically go attend a course for around three weeks and for eight hours a day. You’ll then take a test a become a licensed real estate agent. Here in Colorado Springs, there are several in-person programs you can choose from. My agents have found success in Kaplan, and I personally recommend this option. On top of in-person classes, they also have an online component and correspondence courses. Other real estate schools usually have these components as well.

“Agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests.”

However, I’ve found that agents who take the online and correspondence routes struggle to pass their tests. This is primarily because they’re missing out on vital interaction with an instructor and other benefits of the classroom setting. Correspondence courses, where students are essentially just reading a book, show high failure rates. The online component fares a bit better, but neither option compares to the in-person experience.

Kaplan’s in-person courses see students passing the first or second time, compared to other options where tests are often retaken multiple times. If you want to be better prepared for the final exam, you want to devote three weeks and show up to an in-person class.

If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to contact us. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Becoming a Realtor online sounds like a great option, but students find themselves struggling to keep up. Here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Keys to Making Your Morning Routine More Productive</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-keys-to-making-your-morning-routine.html</link>
        
          <category>Life Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-22 14:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Follow the three components laid out in the book “The Miracle Morning” by Hal Elrod:

1. Read (spiritual or motivational reading)
2. Exercise
3. Coordinate the rest of your day

This is the same routine that I follow every morning. After I wake up at 5:30, I go to the gym and get a workout in. Then I head back home and read scripture and/or part of whatever motivational book I’m reading at the time. I’m learning more and more about meditation, so that’s also something you could try for this step.

When coordinating your day, sit down and fill out your “Dominate Your Day” sheet that I talked about in a previous video. When you plan your day ahead of time, you can focus on it before it gets away from you.

“If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.”

If you have kids, wake up however early you need to to get this done before they get up. The one thing you don’t want to do first thing in the morning is check your smartphone. If you immediately start checking your emails or logging onto Facebook, that will sidetrack your entire day.

If you’d like to talk more about how you can make your morning routine more productive or you have any other questions about this topic, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be glad to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Morning+routine.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to make your morning routine more productive, there are three steps you need to take every day after you wake up.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Can Our Office Provide for You?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-can-our-office-provide-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-04 09:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Visit+Our+Office.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to get an idea of what it’s like working at Jason Daniels &amp; Associates at RE/MAX Millennium, I invite you to take quick tour of our state-of-the-art office. We have a deluxe client waiting room, a spacious cafe for clients and agents, two conference rooms, 13 private offices, and four additional meeting offices. Everywhere you go, you’ll also have the latest technology at your fingertips. On the outside, we’re conveniently located right along the northern powers corridor. To get the full tour, watch this short video.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Key Tips That Will Help You Create a Productive Work Environment</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/key-tips-that-will-help-you-create.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-19 16:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


If you want to grow your business, you need to have a productive work environment.

Some agents like to work from home, and that’s okay. Others like to have their office in an office. Here at RE/MAX Millennium, we offer both options. Either way, you’ll find a great work environment, and in our office, we have a cafe space, inviting decor, and a wonderful administrative team to support all our clients.

In any case, here are a couple tips to help you ensure a productive work environment.

“CREATE A PRODUCTIVE WORK ENVIRONMENT.”

If you work from home and that’s important to you, you should treat your workday just like you would anywhere else. If you’d wear a suit and tie to the office, wear a suit and tie at home. Dress how you’d normally dress, whether you have an appointment or not. Otherwise, you might find yourself sitting on the couch with a bag of Doritos watching TV when you should be prospecting.

It’s also important to have a regimented schedule when you work from home. If you have small children at home or you don’t have your own workspace there, you need to make sure you have a space in the office where you can actually get work done. Stay focused and don’t let yourself get distracted by emails or your smartphone (it’s not so “smart” if it’s distracting you).

Studies have shown that there’s no such thing as multitasking, so take 60- to 90-minute periods throughout the day to focus on one thing. I promise you that if you do this, your productivity will increase, and I have plenty of other productivity hacks that I’d be happy to share with you if you’re interested.

If you have any more questions about how to create a productive work environment or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a shout. I’d be happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Work+environment.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you work from home, you can create a productive work environment by treating your work day just like you would anywhere else.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Rediscover the Lost Art of the Handwritten Note</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-rediscover-lost-art-of.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-28 12:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


With all modern methods of communication available today, like emails, texts, social media, and more, handwritten notes have become a lost art.

Think about it: When is the last time you received a personal, pen-and-paper letter?

Personally, I think reaching out this way is still important. This is why I spend some time each day to write five clients a personal note. Whether it’s an inquiry or simply a message of thanks—there is always a reason to send a handwritten note.

It’s been proven that writing three to five handwritten notes per day will boost your business. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve received a phone call from someone thanking me for taking this extra step in reaching out.

“WHETHER IT’S AN INQUIRY OR SIMPLY A MESSAGE OF THANKS—THERE IS ALWAYS A REASON TO SEND A HANDWRITTEN NOTE.”

Following this simple tip is an easy, inexpensive way to stay at the top of your clients’ minds, all while increasing the chances that they’ll send referral business your way.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Handwritten+note.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Handwritten notes are a powerful, but very underused, means of communication. Today, let’s delve deeper into how pen-and-paper messages can boost your business.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Growing Your Business With Social Media</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-growing-your-business.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-01 13:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


With all of the different social media platforms out there, using them to grow your business can feel overwhelming. However, leveraging platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Snapchat, and Instagram (to name just a few), can be quite effective. The key is to be consistent.

Make sure that you are posting on a daily or weekly basis, and that your posts are appropriate. While it should mostly be business-related, you can also occasionally include personal touches. This way when people Google your name, they’ll be able to learn a little about you before meeting up with you for a listing appointment.

“WHILE IT SHOULD MOSTLY BE BUSINESS-RELATED, YOUR SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNTS CAN ALSO INCLUDE PERSONAL TOUCHES TO HELP POTENTIAL CLIENTS SEE YOU AS A REAL PERSON.”

If you want to keep your private Facebook life locked out, that is fine. That said, creating a Realtor Facebook page or business page will greatly benefit your business. And, if you’re comfortable doing so, adding in the personal things to your real estate page will help others see you as a real person.

Beyond posting, watch your clients and keep in touch with them to change an online situation into a personal situation. You can wish them a happy birthday or send them gifts when they have a new baby. This is especially important if they are someone who would refer you business. Taking these steps will help you build a long-term relationship.

Online interactions with clients can be turned into a source of referral business. The more you do this, the more you are going to win. Of course, you can buy internet leads, but I’m a fan of working by referral and building relationships with clients both online and off.

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me. I look forward to speaking with you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Social+Media.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter can help grow your business if you do it the right way.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Which Leadership Philosophy Should You Use to Guide Your Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/which-leadership-philosophy-should-you.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-06 13:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I’d like to discuss an important concept: leading versus managing.

If you’ve ever been part of a team, you’ve almost certainly encountered one, or both, of these leadership styles. The way a team runs under each will be different, and noticeably so.

So what is the difference between these concepts?

First, managing means that the person in power is simply barking commands. Leading, on the other hand, is all about inspiring those who look to you for guidance.

Rather than simply telling people what to do, leading is all about guiding people toward the right decisions. This is the leadership approach that helps teams succeed.

“LEAD BY INSPIRATION, NOT BY ORDERS.”

For those of you who have a team or are interested in growing one, we would be happy to help you more fully understand how having the right leadership philosophy can benefit a collaborative environment.

Giving your team goals and allowing them to be part of the creative process will improve the results you see from their work. Your team members should feel as if you trust them, and as if they have the power to work autonomously toward the team’s larger objectives.

As a leader, your task is to educate, guide, and work alongside your team. Lead by inspiration, not by orders.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

When you act as the head of a team you can either lead them or manage them, but which is the better approach? Let’s discuss this crucial question.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Our Core Values Mean to Us</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-our-core-values-mean-to-us.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-11 14:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I want to talk to you about core values. Every business owner should have a set of core values that drive the way they do business. Here are the core values we have at RE/MAX Millennium:

“WE EMBRACE SKILLS TRAINING, EDUCATION, AND PERSONAL GROWTH.”

• We always do what’s right, even when nobody’s looking.

• We put people first. People before profits.

• We hold people’s names sacred. We have a no-gossip policy here and we will not tolerate it.

• We’re always teachable and learning. That is why we really embrace skills training, education, and personal growth. We are one of only a few brokerages in town that does this type of program.

• We laugh and we have fun. We are all here to make money, but we have to have fun too.

• We are grateful.

• We are real and transparent. No facades here. You get what you see with us.

• We are one. We are all a team here at RE/MAX Millennium. Anybody in our office can help you and answer any questions at any time.

Those are our eight core values here and it is how we dictate our interactions with our team, our clients, and our community. If you have any questions about our core values or how to create your own, please feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Core+values.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Every business owner needs a set of core values. Here are our core values and what they mean to us.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Makes RE/MAX Millennium a Cut Above the Rest?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-makes-remax-millennium-cut-above.html</link>
        
          <category>For Realtors</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-31 16:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4</guid>
        <description>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


There are many different things our team members cite as being their favorite aspect of RE/MAX Millennium. For some, it’s the teamwork-focused atmosphere, and for others, it’s great energy, or the knowledge that team leaders truly care about everyone’s success.

I’ve been selling real estate for nearly 15 years, but when I opened RE/MAX Millennium it became apparent that there were certain things I was ready to do differently. My team and I were able to redesign our office space and our core values around how we want to run business—which is essentially just an amplified version of what we were doing before.

So far, our team has loved what these changes have done for us and our clients. Broker associate Ron Mast, for example, has been in real estate and the mortgage industry for over 30 years, and he specifically chose to work with us at RE/MAX Millennium because of our great atmosphere.

And our clients love what’s going on at RE/MAX Millennium, too. According to team member and broker associate TJ Chambless, clients are always complimenting our office’s design and technological resources.

But our office isn’t all we’ve got going for us. Broker associate Jenny Daniels points to our team itself—our people—as being an invaluable resource to clients.

The list of benefits our team brings to the industry goes on and on. Broker associate Alan Daniels says our energy is one thing he personally values about working at RE/MAX Millennium. “It’s a great place to bounce ideas off of each other,” he says.

This sense of collaboration is so strong, in fact, that broker associate Marsha Meyer has said working for our team is like being part of a family. “Everyone really cares about making sure that I’m succeeding,” says Marsha.

“AGENTS HERE AT RE/MAX MILLENNIUM HAVE THE CHANCE TO GROW AS PROFESSIONALS, ALL WHILE DRAWING UPON THE EXPERIENCE OF OTHER SUCCESSFUL AGENTS ALL AROUND THEM.”

It’s easy to see that our RE/MAX Millennium team is a cut above the rest. So many of our agents have great things to say about what it’s like to work here, like broker associate Brian Daniels, who says that RE/MAX Millennium “offers more than the average RE/MAX brokerage.”

Specifically, one of the most significant things RE/MAX Millennium offers its agents is an emphasis on continued education, training, and support.

As for myself, I’m just grateful to be able to provide these opportunities for my team and our clients. Agents here at RE/MAX Millennium have the chance to grow as professionals, all while drawing upon the experience of other successful agents all around them.

At RE/MAX Millennium, we hold high ethical standards, provide high levels of support for our agents, and are always working to treat people right. So, if you’re thinking of making a career move, why not consider joining us? We’d love to show you where all this high praise comes from.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+ReMax+Promo+Video.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

RE/MAX Millennium offers much more than your typical brokerage. Today some of our agents are here to tell you about the benefits they enjoy as part of our team.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Hire a Real Estate Coach?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/schedule-free-business-consultation.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-11 14:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Today I want to let you in on what you should know before you hire a real estate coach.

First, do you even need a real estate coach? Even the greats like Tiger Woods and other major athletes have multiple coaches. Coaching is definitely a good way to help hold yourself accountable for your activities and to keep you in line with what’s happening in the current marketplace. With their help, you can understand how to navigate market trends and agent-client interactions.

The great thing about RE/MAX Millennium is that I offer coaching to any agents who want to come to my office. I will teach you and help you grow: I’ve coached with more than four other national coaches, and I even have a coach right now who I’m helping on a weekly basis.

I can share tips and tricks I’ve learned over the many years I’ve been in the real estate industry, working with professionals in prospecting, referrals, team-building, and more. I’ve spent hundreds of thousands of dollars on coaching, and I’m prepared to give you access to that pool of knowledge.

“I OFFER COACHING TO ANY AGENTS WHO WANT TO COME TO MY OFFICE.”

However, if you want to hire a coach, just be aware that it can be costly. Make sure you understand that it’s a time commitment; you might be on a weekly or monthly call or you might get homework assignments. If they’re good, your coach will hold you accountable.

You’ll also want to have a clear perspective on your goals. There are different types of coaches who specialize in different areas, so you’ll need to know what you want to learn from them and why before you select one to hire.

Finally, you’ll need to reach out and get testimonials from the coach’s clients, or else speak with agents who have worked with them, in order to make sure their process is legitimate and that they have successfully helped agents grow their business.

As a coaching expert, I’m happy to sit down with you and help you. If you have a question about a specific coach, I’ve done research on almost all of them, and I’d gladly share my thoughts with you. Please feel free to reach out to me by phone or email. I hope to hear from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+What+you+should+know.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There is a lot of value in hiring a real estate coach. Today I’ll share what you stand to gain and what you should think about before hiring one.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Boost Your Productivity Using These 2 Tips</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/boost-your-productivity-using-these-2.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-04-19 13:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


There are a number of things you can do to increase your productivity without increasing the number of hours you spend working.

My first recommendation for boosting productivity is by implementing a tool called “Dominate Your Day”, or DYD. This tool prioritizes your day by listing the six most important dollar-producing activities you should be taking on. The tool also outlines your goals. If you’d like a copy of this, please let me know and I’d be happy to send you a copy.

“TIME BLOCKING IS THE GREATEST PRODUCTIVITY BOOSTER I CAN RECOMMEND.”

The second recommendation I have for increasing your productivity is carving out your calendar and implementing time blocking. This is a tip you’ve probably heard time and time again, but that’s because it works. Agents who time block can double or even triple their success. Time blocking is as simple as assigning specific tasks to specific hours of each day.

For example, my team and I have a huddle from 8:30 a.m. to 8:45 a.m. every single day. Of course, it’s also important to block off time for leisure, family, and vacation. I actually recommend blocking this time off first. Time blocking is the greatest productivity booster I can recommend.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Increase+productivity.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you want to increase your productivity, I highly recommend that you implement the two things I’m about to share with you today.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can Texting Improve Your Conversion Rate?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-texting-improve-your-conversion.html</link>
        
          <category>Realtor Tools</category>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-03-21 11:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


Should you text your leads? Well, based on what we’ve found, our team and others are actually getting a far better response rate with texting than with calling.

Obviously, we like to call people when we first reach out since voice-to-voice contact still plays an important role. However, these days, most people let their phone go to voicemail.

You can call up to three times without leaving a message if you’re bold. They may answer if you are this persistent. But if they don’t, I recommend leaving a voicemail and also following up with a text message saying who you are and that you’d be happy to assist them with their real estate needs.

“IF YOU HAVEN’T BEEN DOING SO ALREADY, TEXT THOSE LEADS!”

There are text systems you can buy, but your phone is all you really need. If you haven’t been doing so already, text those leads! It will make a big difference in your conversation rate.

You can find samples of texts we’ve used to convert leads here, or here.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Daniels/2018/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Texting+your+leads.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Should you be texting your leads? Absolutely! Here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>6 Books That All Successful People Should Read</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/6-books-that-all-successful-people.html</link>
        
        <author>Jason Daniels</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-08 10:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.


Schedule a free business consultation
Selling your Colorado home? Get a free home value report  
Buying a Colorado home? Search all homes for sale


One of the biggest sources of inspiration and motivation for me is the books that I’ve read. There are a number of books that I can point to that have helped me grow both professionally and personally. I believe that reading is a key to success, which is why I have a library for my team that is always growing. Here are a few of my favorite books that taught me countless lessons about real estate and business in general:

• “Think and Grow Rich” by Napoleon Hill
• “Millionaire Real Estate Agent” by Gary Keller
• “How to Win Friends and Influence People” by Dale Carnegie
• “The E-Myth” by Michael Gerber
• “Eat That Frog!” by Brian Tracy
• “Fanatical Prospecting” by Jeb Blount

Reading these books will help you take your business and transform it into a career and a lifestyle that will help you build the life you want. These are just a handful at the ones at the top of my list, so if you have any suggestions, I’d love to hear them. If you have any other questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Gary+Kent/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate-+Books.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Daniels</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There are a number of different books that have helped me take my career to the next level. Here are six of them.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Colorado Springs, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jason Daniels</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jason Daniels</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from RE/MAX Millennium - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
